Rylʹsʹkyĭ Institute Ukrainian Cylinder Collection, 1908-1930s
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series II: Sound Recordings
  - Psalm about Lazarus Псальма про Лазаря Sung by an unidentified performer Psalm, voice, solo, male Song index number: 52.0 Cylinder index number: 35/80 (Tape-id AFC 1992/005: SR09)
  - Psalm Псальма Sung by an unidentified performer Psalm, bandura, male Song index number: 53.0 Cylinder index number: 35/81
  - Duma about Oleksi Popovych (continuation) Дума Про Олексiя Поповича (продовження) Sung by an unidentified performer Duma, voice, lira (hurdy-gurdy), male Song index number: 54.0 Cylinder index number: 35/83
  - Duma "Hey, on the Black Sea" Дума "Гей, на Чорному Морi" Sung by an unidentified performer Duma, voice, lira (hurdy-gurdy), male Song index number: 54.1 Cylinder index number: 35/83
  - Keening for mother Голосiння за мамою Sung by an unidentified performer Funeral lament (Keening), voice, solo, female Song index number: 55.0 Cylinder index number: 35/85
  - Female solo singing, Keening for mother Жiночий сольоспiв, Голосiння за мамою Sung by an unidentified performer Funeral lament (Keening), voice, solo, female Song index number: 56.0 Cylinder index number: 35/86
  - Psalm about Lazarus Псальма про Лазаря Sung and played by Nazar Poklad Psalm, voice, lira (hurdy-gurdy), male Song index number: 57.0 Cylinder index number: 35/87
  - Keening, and second голосiння Sung by an unidentified performer Funeral lament, voice, solo, female Song index number: 58.0 Cylinder index number: 35/88 (Tape-id AFC 1992/005: SR10)
  - sopilka (a folk flute) music гра на сопiлцi Played by an unidentified performer Instrumental, sopilka (folk flute) Song index number: 58.1 Cylinder index number: 35/88
  - Iivha Hrishchenko, begging for alms Ўвга Грищенко, жебрання Sung by Iivha Hrishchenko Begging, voice, female Song index number: 59.0 Cylinder index number: 35/89
  - Iivha Hrishchenko, Keening for deceased brother Ўвга Грищенко, Голосiння за братом Sung by Iivha Hrishchenko Funeral lament (Keening), voice, female Song index number: 60.0 Cylinder index number: 35/90
  - Begging for alms Жiночий сольоспiв, жебрання Sung by an unidentified performer Begging, voice, female Song index number: 61.0 Cylinder index number: 35/91
  - "In Mourning" "На Жалоб" Sung and played by Nestir Kolisnyk Song, lira (hurdy-gurdy), male Song index number: 62.0 Cylinder index number: 35/93
  - Poltavochka Полтавочка Played by Nazar Poklad Dance, lira (hurdy-gurdy), male Song index number: 63.0 Cylinder index number: 35/94
  - Dudochka Дудочка Played by Nazar Poklad Dance, lira (hurdy-gurdy), male Song index number: 63.1 Cylinder index number: 35/94
  - "Oh, it was Summer" "Ой, було лiто" Sung by Ms. Sochotsʹka Song, voice, female Song index number: 64.0 Cylinder index number: 35/95
  - "Oh Harsh Winter" "Ой, зима лютая" Sung by Ms. Sochotsʹka Song, voice, female Song index number: 64.1 Cylinder index number: 35/95
  - Dudochka Дудочка Played by Ivan Semenishyn Dance, dudna (folk flute), female Song index number: 65.0 Cylinder index number: 35/96
  - Barynia Бариня Played by Ivan Semenishyn Dance, dudna (folk flute), female Song index number: 65.1 Cylinder index number: 35/96
  - Kamarynsʹka Камаринська Played by Ivan Semenishyn Dance, dudna (folk flute), female Song index number: 65.2 Cylinder index number: 35/96
  - Choboty Чоботи Played by Ivan Semenishyn Dance, dudna (folk flute), female Song index number: 65.3 Cylinder index number: 35/96
  - Kozachok Козачок Played by Ivan Semenishyn Dance, dudna (folk flute), female Song index number: 65.4 Cylinder index number: 35/96
  - Ovcharna Овчарна Played by Ivan Semenishyn Dance, dudna (folk flute), female Song index number: 65.5 Cylinder index number: 35/96
  - Kubanochka Кубаночка Played by Ivan Semenishyn Dance, dudna (folk flute), male Song index number: 65.6 Cylinder index number: 35/96
  - About Lazar про Лазаря Played by Ivan Semenishyn Dance, dudna (folk flute), male Song index number: 65.7 Cylinder index number: 35/96
  - Poltavochka Полтавочка Sung and played by Nazar Poklad Dance, lira (hurdy-gurdy), male Song index number: 66.0 Cylinder index number: 35/97 (Tape-id AFC 1992/005: SR11)
  - Kamarynsʹka Камаринська Sung and played by Nazar Poklad Dance, lira (hurdy-gurdy), male Song index number: 66.1 Cylinder index number: 35/97
  - Hopachok Гопачок Sung and played by Nazar Poklad Dance, lira (hurdy-gurdy), male Song index number: 66.2 Cylinder index number: 35/97
  - "The Fog, Mother, is in the Ravine" "Туман, мати, за яром" Sung by an unidentified performer Song, voice Song index number: 67.0 Cylinder index number: 35/98
  - Song about a mother Пiсня про неньку Sung by an unidentified performer Song, voice Song index number: 68.0 Cylinder index number: 35/99
  - Labor song Строкарська пiсня, та Sung by an unidentified performer Song (work), voice Song index number: 69.0 Cylinder index number: 35/100
  - "The Cuckoo Cuckoo'ed" "Закувала зозуленька," Sung by an unidentified performer Song, voice Song index number: 69.1 Cylinder index number: 35/100
  - Oh, the valley, mother "Ой гай, мамцю, гай" Sung by an unidentified performer Song, voice Song index number: 69.2 Cylinder index number: 35/100
  - "There was a village Vasylʹov" "Було село Васильове" Sung by an unidentified performer Song (Bandit) voice Song index number: 70.0 Cylinder index number: 35/101
  - "My Mother Called Me to Reap the Green Wheat" "Звала мене мати зелене жито жати" Sung by an unidentified performer Song, voice Song index number: 71.0 Cylinder index number: 35/102
  - Untitled song Пісня Sung by an unidentified performer Song, voice Song index number: 71.1 Cylinder index number: 35/102
  - "King," a Spring song Веснянка "Король" Sung by an unidentified performer Ritual Song (Spring), voice Song index number: 72.0 Cylinder index number: 35/103
  - Group singing, carol Гуртовий спiв, колядка Sung by an unidentified performer Ritual Song (Winter, Koliadka), voice Song index number: 73.0 Cylinder index number: 35/104
  - Untitled song Двi пiснi Sung by an unidentified performer Song, voice Song index number: 74.0 Cylinder index number: 35/105
  - Untitled song Двi пiснi Song, voice Sung by an unidentified performer Song index number: 74.1 Cylinder index number: 35/105
  - "The Grove Does Not Sway without the Wind" "Дiброва без вiтру не шумить" Sung by Maria Shevchenkova Song, voice, female Song index number: 75.0 Cylinder index number: 35/106 (Tape-id AFC 1992/005: SR12)
  - Spring song: "Oh, Mice Ran in Grandma's House" Веснянка: "Ой, бiгали мишi по бабинi хатi" Sung by Maria Shevchenkova Ritual song (Spring), voice, female Song index number: 76.0 Cylinder index number: 35/107
  - Spring song: "The Cuckoo Is Not in the Garden" Веснянка: "Нема в саду зозуленьки" Sung by Maria Shevchenkova Ritual song (Spring), voice, female Song index number: 76.1 Cylinder index number: 35/107
  - Sopilka (folk flute) tune: untitled Гра на сопiлцi Played by Kornylo Bojko sopilka (folk flute), male Song index number: 77.0 Cylinder index number: 35/108
  - Sopilka (folk flute) tune: untitled Гра на сопiлцi sopilka (folk flute), male Song index number: 78.0 Cylinder index number: 35/109
  - Sopilka (folk flute) tune: untitled Гра на сопiлцi sopilka (folk flute), male Song index number: 79.0 Cylinder index number: 35/110
  - Sopilka (folk flute) tune: untitled Гра на сопiлцi sopilka (folk flute), male Song index number: 80.0 Cylinder index number: 35/112
  - Sopilka (folk flute) tune: untitled Гра на сопiлцi sopilka (folk flute), male Song index number: 81.0 Cylinder index number: 35/113
  - Sopilka (folk flute) tune: untitled Гра на сопiлцi sopilka (folk flute), male Song index number: 82.0 Cylinder index number: 35/114 (Tape-id AFC 1992/005: SR13)
  - "Thoughts of a Ploughman" Думки хлiборобiв Sung by an unidentified performer Song, voice Song index number: 83.0 Cylinder index number: 35/115
  - "You Black Field" "Чорне Твоє поле" Sung by an unidentified performer Song, voice Song index number: 83.1 Cylinder index number: 35/115
  - Song about the revolt in Turbaiiv Пiсня про Турбаўвське повстання Sung by an unidentified performer Song, voice Song index number: 84.0 Cylinder index number: 35/116
  - Song about the revolt in Turbaiiv Пiсня про Турбаўвське повстання Sung by Pylyp Litvinenʹko Song, voice, male Song index number: 85.0 Cylinder index number: 35/117
  - Song about the revolt in Turbaiiv Пiсня про Турбаўвське повстання Pylyp Litvinenʹko? Song, voice, male Song index number: 86.0 Cylinder index number: 35/118
  - Song about the revolt in Turbaiiv Пiсня про Турваўвське повстання Hryhory Shevchenko Song, voice, male Song index number: 87.0 Cylinder index number: 35/119
  - Song about the revolt in Turbaiiv Пiсня про Турваўвське повстання Hryhory Shevchenko Song, voice, male Song index number: 88.0 Cylinder index number: 35/120
  - Song about the revolt in Turbaiiv Пiсня про Турваўвське повстання Hryhory Shevchenko Song, voice, male Song index number: 89.0 Cylinder index number: 35/121
  - Group singing, untitled song Гуртовий спiв: пiсня без назви Sung by unidentified performers Song, voice, female Song index number: 90.0 Cylinder index number: 35/123 (Tape-id AFC 1992/005: SR14)
  - Group singing, untitled song [this may be continuation of previous song. -AP] Гуртовий спiв: пiсня без назви Sung by unidentified performers Song Song index number: 90.1 Cylinder index number: 35/123
  - Untitled song Солоспів: Пісня без назви Sung by an unidentified performer Song, voice, male Song index number: 91.0 Cylinder index number: 35/124
  - Untitled song Солоспів: Пісня без назви Sung by an unidentified performer Song, voice, male Song index number: 91.1 Cylinder index number: 35/124
  - Untitled song [possibly continuation of previous song. -AP] Солоспів: Пісня без назви Sung by an unidentified performer Song, voice, male Song index number: 91.2 Cylinder index number: 35/124
  - "Turbaiiv" "Турбаўвка" Sung by Maria Malenka Song, voice, female Song index number: 92.0 Cylinder index number: 35/129
  - [Possibly additional untitled song on this cylinder not documented] Sung by Maria Malenka Song, voice, female Song index number: 92.1 Cylinder index number: 35/129
  - Untitled dance tune [on a dudna, flute-like instrument, AP] Гра на дудi без назви Played by Grandpa Polukash Dance, dudna (folk flute), male Song index number: 93.0 Cylinder index number: 35/132
  - Untitled dance tune [on a dudna, flute-like instrument, AP] Гра на дудi без назви Played by Grandpa Polukash Dance, dudna (folk flute), male Song index number: 93.1 Cylinder index number: 35/132
  - Song to "weeding" Пiсня до полення Sung by an unidentified performer Ritual (de-weeding), voice, female Song index number: 94.0 Cylinder index number: 35/133
  - Singing with instrumental ensemble (Southwestern Ukraine) Сольоспiв з iнструментальним супроводом, iз Пiвденнозахiдної Украiни Sung and played by unidentified performers Song, voice, fiddle, durm, male Song index number: 95.0 Cylinder index number: 35/134
  - Singing with instrumental ensemble (Southwestern Ukraine) [possibly continuation from previous cylinder, also an additional composition only with instruments without voice, AP] Сольоспiв з iнструментальним супроводом, iз Пiвденнозахiдної Украiни Sung and played by unidentified performers Song, voice, fiddle, durm, male Song index number: 96.0 Cylinder index number: 35/135
  - [an additional composition only with instruments without voice, AP] Інструментальний ансамбль iз Пiвденнозахiдної Украiни Instrumental, fiddle, drum Song index number: 96.1 Cylinder index number: 35/135
  - Female group singing Жiночий гуртовий спiв Sung by unidentified performers Song, female Song index number: 97.0 Cylinder index number: 35/136 (Tape-id AFC 1992/005: SR15)
  - Instrumental ensemble Iнструментальний ансамбль Played by unidentified performers Instrumental Song index number: 98.0 Cylinder index number: 35/137
  - Untitled song for hurdy-gurdy Гра на лiрi без назви Sung and played by unidentified performers Instrumental, song, lira (hurdy-gurdy) Song index number: 99.0 Cylinder index number: 35/138
  - Untitled song for hurdy-gurdy Гра на лiрi без назви Sung and played by unidentified performers Instrumental, song, lira (hurdy-gurdy) Song index number: 99.1 Cylinder index number: 35/138
  - Untitled song for hurdy-gurdy Спів із супроводом на лiрi Sung and played by unidentified performers Instrumental Song, voice, lira (hurdy-gurdy) Song index number: 99.2 Cylinder index number: 35/138
  - Solo singing Сольоспiв Sung by an unidentified performer Song, voice Song index number: 100.0 Cylinder index number: 35/139
  - Female Solo singing and male group singing Жiночий сольоспiв та мужеський гуртовий спiв Sung by an unidentified performer Song, voice, female and male Song index number: 101.0 Cylinder index number: 35/140
  - Psalm "Jesus, my beloved" "Iсусе, мой прелюбезний" Sung and played by Ivan Bednarsky Psalm, voice, lira (hurdy-gurdy), male Song index number: 102.0 Cylinder index number: 35/141
  - Psalm "Jesus, my beloved" (continuation) "Iсусе, мой прелюбезний" (продовження) Sung and played by Ivan Bednarsky Psalm voice, lira (hurdy-gurdy), male Song index number: 103.0 Cylinder index number: 35/141
  - Untitled song: Female group singing Пісня без назви: жiночий гуртовий спiв Sung by unidentified performers Song, choir, female Song index number: 104.0 Cylinder index number: 35/143
  - Untitled song: Female group singing Пісня без назви: жiночий гуртовий спiв Sung by unidentified performers Song, choir, female Song index number: 105.0 Cylinder index number: 35/144 (Tape-id AFC 1992/005: SR16)
  - Untitled song: Female group singing Пісня без назви: жiночий гуртовий спiв Sung by unidentified performers Song, choir, female Song index number: 105.1 Cylinder index number: 35/144
  - Untitled song: Female group singing Пісня без назви: жiночий гуртовий спiв Sung by unidentified performers Song, choir, female Song index number: 106.0 Cylinder index number: 35/145
  - Untitled song: Female group singing Пісня без назви: жiночий гуртовий спiв Sung by unidentified performers Song, choir, female Song index number: 106.1 Cylinder index number: 35/145
  - Group: "She Walked, Wandered in the Cherry Orchard" Гуртовий спiв: "Ходила блукала в вишневiм саду" Sung by unidentified performers Song, choir Song index number: 107.0 Cylinder index number: 35/146
  - Group: "Why Do I Hedge My Land?" "Нащо менi город городити" Sung by unidentified performers Song, choir Song index number: 107.1 Cylinder index number: 35/146
  - Solo singing,"Oh, Come Out" Сольоспiв: "Ой, вийди" Sung by an unidentified performer Song Song index number: 107.2 Cylinder index number: 35/146
  - Жiночий гуртовий спiв, пісня без навзи Female group singing, untitled song Sung by unidentified performers Song, choir, female Song index number: 108.0 Cylinder index number: 35/147
  - Female group singing, untitled song Жiночий гуртовий спiв, пісня без навзи Sung by unidentified performers Song, choir, female Song index number: 108.1 Cylinder index number: 35/147
  - "Oh, to Resemble" "Ой, похожено" Sung by unidentified performers Song, voice, duet, female Song index number: 109.0 Cylinder index number: 35/148
  - "On This Side" "По тiм боцi" Sung by unidentified performers Song, voice, duet, female Song index number: 109.1 Cylinder index number: 35/148
  - "The Fog in the Ravine" "Туман яром" Sung by unidentified performers Song, voice, duet, female Song index number: 109.2 Cylinder index number: 35/148
  - Untitled male duet singing Пісня без назви: мужеський дует Sung by unidentified performers Song, voice, duet, male Song index number: 110.0 Cylinder index number: 35/149
  - Untitled male duet singing Пісня без назви: мужеський дует Sung by unidentified performers Song, voice, duet, male Song index number: 110.1 Cylinder index number: 35/149
  - Untitled male duet singing Пісня без назви: мужеський дует Sung by unidentified performers Song, voice, duet, male Song index number: 110.2 Cylinder index number: 35/149
  - Untitled wedding song Весільна пісня без назви Sung by unidentified performers Song (wedding), choir, female Song index number: 111.0 Cylinder index number: 35/150
  - Untitled song "Ой, Пришляк" Sung by unidentified performers Song (wedding), choir, female Song index number: 111.1 Cylinder index number: 35/150
  - "Kozachok" "Козачок" Sung by unidentified performers Song (wedding), choir, ensemble, female Song index number: 111.2 Cylinder index number: 35/150
  - "Oh, Why Is It So Hard for Me?" Жiночий гуртовий спiв, "Ой, чогож менi тяжко, важко" Sung by unidentified performers Song, choir, female Song index number: 112.0 Cylinder index number: 35/161
  - Untitled song Пісня без назви: гуртовий спів Sung by unidentified performers Song, choir Song index number: 113.0 Cylinder index number: 35/216
  - Untitled song Пісня без назви: гуртовий спів Sung by unidentified performers Song, choir, female Song index number: 113.1 Cylinder index number: 35/216
  - Untitled song: female group singing Пісня без назви: жiночий гуртовий спiв Sung by an unidentified performer Song, solo voice, a cappella, female Song index number: 114.0 Cylinder index number: 35/169 (Tape-id AFC 1992/005: SR17)
  - Пісня без назви:жiноче соло Untitled song: female solo Sung by an unidentified performer Song, solo voice, a cappella, female Song index number: 114.1 Cylinder index number: 35/169
  - Untitled song: female duet Пісня без назви:жiночий дует Sung by unidentified performers Song, voice, duet, female Song index number: 114.2 Cylinder index number: 35/169
  - Untitled song: male solo Пісня без назви: чоловіче соло Sung by an unidentified performer Song index number: 114.3 Song, solo voice, a cappella, male Cylinder index number: 35/169
  - Untitled song: male solo Пісня без назви: чоловіче соло Sung by an unidentified performer Song index number: 114.4 Song, solo voice, a cappella, male Cylinder index number: 35/169
  - "Did You Brothers Hear?" "Чи Ви браття зачували?" Sung by unidentified performers Song, choir, female Song index number: 115.0 Cylinder index number: 35/228
  - "In the Green Valley" "У зеленiм гаю" Sung by unidentified performers Song, choir, female Song index number: 115.1 Cylinder index number: 35/228
  - "When I Wash My Sleeves" "Коли я рукава мила" Sung by unidentified performers Song, choir, female Song index number: 115.2 Cylinder index number: 35/228
  - "Oh, the Girl Walked in the Forest" "Ой, iшла дiвчина в лiс" Sung by unidentified performers Song, choir, female Song index number: 115.3 Cylinder index number: 35/228
  - "Why Do You Not Come to Us, Ivan?" "Чому Ти, Iване, до нас не ходиш?" Sung by an unidentified performer Song, voice, solo, male Song index number: 116.0 Cylinder index number: 35/239
  - "My First Girlfriend is Sad" "Сумна моя перша наречена Sung by an unidentified performer Song, voice, solo, male Song index number: 116.1 Cylinder index number: 35/239
  - "They Did Not Dare, My Dear Mother" "Не смiла мя, моя люба мамо" Sung by an unidentified performer Song, voice, solo, male Song index number: 116.2 Cylinder index number: 35/239
  - "Christ, the Saviour, Was Born" "Христос, Спаситель, народився" Sung by unidentified performers Song, choir Song index number: 116.3 Cylinder index number: 35/239
  - "Where is the Star?" "Де ота звiздиця" Sung by unidentified performers Song, choir Song index number: 116.4 Cylinder index number: 35/239
  - "The Star Circled the Earth" "Iшла звiздиця край свiта" Sung by unidentified performers Song, choir Song index number: 116.5 Cylinder index number: 35/239
  - "In the Green Grove" "В зеленiм гаєчку" Sung by unidentified performers Song, choir Song index number: 116.6 Cylinder index number: 35/239
  - "Down by the Green Forest," "Попiд лiсом зелененьким" Sung by unidentified performers Song, choir Song index number: 116.7 Cylinder index number: 35/239
  - "Finally, the Family is in the Country" "Вже родина в краю" Sung by unidentified performers Song, choir Song index number: 116.8 Cylinder index number: 35/239
  - "On this Night, at Midnight" "Цiєў ночi, о пiвночi" Sung by unidentified performers Song, choir Song index number: 117.0 Cylinder index number: 35/240
  - "We Praise You" "Величаєм Тя," Sung by unidentified performers Song, choir Song index number: 117.1 Cylinder index number: 35/240
  - "Time has Come" "Прийшов час" Sung by unidentified performers Song, choir Song index number: 117.2 Cylinder index number: 35/240
  - "Font of Tears" "Iсточника сльоз" Sung by unidentified performers Song, choir Song index number: 117.3 Cylinder index number: 35/240
  - "Oh White, Fine Fish" "Ай, бiла файна рибка" Sung by unidentified performers Song, choir Song index number: 117.4 Cylinder index number: 35/240
  - "Come Out, Fairskinned Girl" "Ой, вийди, бiла дiвка" Sung by unidentified performers Song, choir Song index number: 117.5 Cylinder index number: 35/240
  - "Many years" "Многая літа" Sung by an unidentified performer Song Song index number: 118.0 Cylinder index number: 35/263
  - Song medley Співанка Sung by an unidentified performer Song Song index number: 118.1 Cylinder index number: 35/263
  - Wedding song Весільна пісня Sung by an unidentified performer Song Song index number: 118.2 Cylinder index number: 35/263
  - "As I Was Walking along the Valley" "Шов я поруч гай" Sung by an unidentified performer Song, voice, solo Song index number: 119.0 Cylinder index number: 35/266
  - "Grass, Grass" "Травка, травка" Sung by an unidentified performer Song, voice, solo Song index number: 119.1 Cylinder index number: 35/266
  - "Day, Day" "День, день" Sung by an unidentified performer Song, voice, solo Song index number: 119.2 Cylinder index number: 35/266
  - Commercial recording of Overture from the opera "Fra Diavolo" Комерцiйне награння овертюри iз опери "Фра Дiавол" Song index number: 120.0 Cylinder index number: 53
  - Untitled song: female group singing Пісня без навзи: жiночий гуртовий спiв Sung by unidentified performers Song, choir Song index number: 121.0 Cylinder index number: 35/175 (Tape-id AFC 1992/005: SR18)
  - Untitled song: female group singing Пісня без навзи: жiночий гуртовий спiв Sung by unidentified performers Song, choir Song index number: 121.1 Cylinder index number: 35/175
  - Untitled song: female group singing Пісня без навзи: жiночий гуртовий спiв Sung by unidentified performers Song, choir Song index number: 121.2 Cylinder index number: 35/175
  - Untitled song: male solo singing Пісня без назви: мужеський сольоспiв Sung by an unidentified performer Song, voice, solo, male Song index number: 122.0 Cylinder index number: 35/176
  - Untitled song: male solo singing Пісня без назви: мужеський сольоспiв Sung by an unidentified performer Song, voice, solo, male Song index number: 122.1 Cylinder index number: 35/176
  - "Oh, Do Not Torment the Martyr" "Ой, не мучай" Sung and played by Ihor Movchan Song, bandura, male Song index number: 123.0 Cylinder index number: 35/177
  - "The Ballad of Sava Chaly" "Про Саву Чалочо" Sung by Ihor Movchan Song, voice, solo, male Song index number: 123.1 Cylinder index number: 35/177
  - Duma about three brothers and poetry declamation Дума про троьх братiв Sung and played by Hrytsʹko Oblichenko Duma, voice, lira (hurdy-gurdy), male Song index number: 124.0 Cylinder index number: 35/184
  - "Oh, All the Fields Have Blackened" "Ой, усi поля почорнiли" Spoken by Hrytsʹko Oblichenko Poetry declamation, voice, solo, male Song index number: 124.1 Cylinder index number: 35/184
  - Untitled song: female group singing Пісня без назви: жiночий гуртовий спiв Sung by unidentified performers Song, choir, female Song index number: 125.0 Cylinder index number: 35/185 (Tape-id AFC 1992/005: SR19)